{
    "id": "64e942aaf54445e78221dd038265bf7b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Theresa has been married …………….. Charles for thirty years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7ea72897ccd405d8c9c6eabe936e3b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alex is married ……………….. three kids.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f86af9bd76ee4ed89f49942167a0fd5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your hair color is similar ……………….. mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59a7110f55d84638a2b2a16b5a898520"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is interested ……………….. philosophy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2a6e849533648db8341ee25623a52b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are responsible ………………. the mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eafaed96daa343c1a4ae2c194acaabd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is typical ………………… her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07e7145f04324f46958cd9d72822dce4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sick ……………….. his erratic behavior.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f781fa2f665d4e669d4352c4f0c6f2d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is quite capable ………………. defending himself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c2801bfec6384e5aa86121e97850355b"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I was short ……………… cash, I borrowed some from my uncle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52b3ea3502874772b10c93bceba1aec6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wasn’t aware …………………. his motives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f49888134a64f10895ec92aff904bd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie is quite good …………………. solving puzzles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b1f46b4a9db4bf4badcd524ad26bf3c"
        }
    ]
}